<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<addon id="plugin.video.orion" name="Orion" version="3.7.13" provider-name="zeus768">
    <requires>
        <import addon="xbmc.python" version="3.0.0"/>
        <import addon="script.module.resolveurl" version="5.0.0" optional="true"/>
        <import addon="script.module.zeusresolvers" version="1.0.0" optional="true"/>
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource" library="main.py">
        <provides>video</provides>
    </extension>
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
        <summary lang="en">Orion Media Explorer</summary>
        <description lang="en">Orion v3.7.0 - Complete media addon with Netflix-style interface. BIG poster cards, cyan (#00D4FF) theme. Netflix-style views for History, Favorites, Continue Watching. Netflix-style Trakt integration. Netflix-style Settings panel. Season dropdown and episode grid. Master skin toggle in Settings to switch between Netflix and classic list view.</description>
        <news>[3.7.12] FIX: Playback no longer re-resolves the link or shows "Playback failed" before finally starting. play_source() now hands the resolved stream URL to Kodi via setResolvedUrl(HANDLE, True, ...) instead of calling xbmc.Player().play() directly and then signalling failure with setResolvedUrl(False). Eliminates the "Resolving with Real-Debrid..." → "Playback failed" → "Resolving with Real-Debrid..." loop seen on every play. Also sets ListItem.setContentLookup(False) so Kodi doesn't HEAD-probe the debrid hotlink (some hosts 403 the probe and abort playback). [3.7.11] Fix: "Resolving with Real-Debrid..." (and the Premiumize / AllDebrid / TorBox variants) progress dialog could stay visible on top of the player after the stream had already started playing. play_source() now uses a non-modal background progress dialog (DialogProgressBG) via a small _BGProgress adapter, so the resolver / debrid services keep calling .create / .update / .close exactly as before but the dialog never collides with the video window. [3.7.10] Fix: the "Resolving link..." / "Waiting for TorBox..." progress dialog and the Kodi "Working..." spinner no longer linger on top of the video after playback starts. play_source now signals plugin completion via setResolvedUrl, force-closes any residual progress/busy dialogs after Player.play(), and the TorBox resolver no longer hammers the dialog with redundant updates that pinned it on-screen. [3.7.9] TorBox: authorization now supports BOTH API key entry and the official Device Code flow (with QR code) — pick your preferred method when you tap Authorize TorBox. Verification page: torbox.app/oauth/device. [3.7.8] TorBox: simpler API key authorization (no more device-code wait), faster magnet resolution, batch cache check now uses POST/JSON for accuracy. Netflix-style skin is now OFF by default — enable it from Settings &gt; Appearance if you want the new look. [3.7.6] PunchPlay.tv is BETA / placeholder. The full Trakt-parity menu (watchlist, collection, watched, lists, recommendations, trending, popular, scrobbling) is wired up, but not every endpoint on the PunchPlay backend is live yet — some lists may return empty until the PunchPlay team finishes their public API. Banners and labels added everywhere PunchPlay appears so users know what to expect. [3.7.5] PunchPlay.tv now has full Trakt-parity: watchlist, collection, watched history, custom &amp; liked lists, recommendations, trending and popular. Right-click context menu supports Remove from Watchlist/Collection/History/List. Netflix-style PunchPlay submenu. Auto-mark watched at 80%+ (movies and episodes). Settings &gt; PunchPlay now accepts your Client ID and Client Secret. [3.7.4] Fix: Trakt list items can now be removed via right-click context menu (custom lists, collection, watched history). New: PunchPlay.tv integration — device-code login + automatic scrobbling alongside Trakt during episode playback. Settings &gt; PunchPlay to authorize. [3.7.0] Netflix-style History, Favorites, Continue Watching grids. Netflix-style Settings panel. All views use proper poster art. Trakt fully skinned. Master skin toggle controls everything. [3.6.2] Wider poster tiles, SEASONS button fix, back navigation fix.</news>
        <platform>all</platform>
        <license>GPL-3.0</license>
        <assets>
            <icon>icon.png</icon>
            <fanart>fanart.jpg</fanart>
        </assets>
    </extension>
</addon>
