<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<addon id="plugin.video.salts" version="2.4.2" name="SALTS - Stream All The Sources" provider-name="tknorris, zeus768">
    <requires>
        <import addon="xbmc.python" version="3.0.0"/>
        <import addon="script.module.resolveurl" version="5.1.0"/>
        <import addon="script.module.beautifulsoup4" version="4.9.0"/>
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource" library="default.py">
        <provides>video</provides>
    </extension>
    <extension point="xbmc.service" library="service.py" start="startup"/>
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
        <summary lang="en_GB">Stream All The Sources - Modernized for Kodi 21+</summary>
        <description lang="en_GB">SALTS is a multi-source video addon with 34+ scrapers across torrent sites, streaming sources, anime trackers, and international sources.

Features:
- Custom source dialog with quality breakdown
- Up Next: auto-play next episode for TV series
- Skip Intro prompt for TV episodes
- Torrent Sites: 1337x, YTS, EZTV, TorrentGalaxy, TPB, NNM-Club, RuTracker, RuTor, Nyaa, etc.
- Jackett/Prowlarr Integration: Connect to any indexer
- Debrid Services: Real-Debrid, Premiumize, AllDebrid, TorBox
- Trakt.tv: Watchlists, collections, scrobbling, history
- ResolveURL for 270+ hosting sites

Revived and modernized by zeus768 for Kodi 21 Omega and above.
Original author: tknorris
Thank you to Mister X and Zaxxon709</description>
        <platform>all</platform>
        <license>GPL-3.0-only</license>
        <website>https://github.com/zeus768/plugin.video.salts</website>
        <source>https://github.com/zeus768/plugin.video.salts</source>
        <news>
v2.1.8 (2026)
- Fixed: Source dialog rendering - moved to inline native Kodi Dialog().select() with color-coded formatting
- Fixed: Eliminated external module dependency for source dialog (no more import failures)
- Added: Quality color badges inline (gold 4K, green 1080p, blue 720p, purple 480p, gray SD)
- Added: CACHED/FREE tags, seed health coloring, file sizes all in native dialog

v2.1.7 (2026)
- Added: Bento UI Source Dialog - custom skin with quality-colored badges, cached/free tags, seeds, size
- Added: Pre-Scrape hover caching - background scrape after 2s hover on movie items (4-link rule)
- Added: 24hr TTL hover cache in SQLite for instant source availability
- Added: "Instant!" notification when pre-scraped sources are available
- Added: Clear Pre-Scrape Cache in Tools menu
- Added: Fallback to standard dialog if skin XML not available

v2.1.6 (2026)
- Added: Franchises menu (30 curated + search with unlimited pagination via TMDB collections)
- Added: Actors menu (Popular actors with pagination + search + full filmography with pagination)
- Added: 24/7 Movie Channels - pick an actor, shuffles all their movies, autoplay marathon (max 1080p)
- Added: 24/7 TV Channels - pick a show, random season/episode start, plays sequentially
- Added: Search for franchises, actors, and 24/7 channels

v2.1.5 (2026)
- Added: TorBox debrid service support (API key auth, magnet resolve, cache check)
- Added: Batch cache checking - all scraped torrents checked against debrid services in one pass
- Added: [CACHED] tag and green highlighting for pre-cached sources in source dialog
- Added: Debrid gate - torrent scrapers blocked until a debrid service is enabled
- Added: Source sorting now prioritizes cached torrents
- Fixed: Replaced all 'requests' usage with native urllib in base_scraper.py and debrid.py
- Fixed: All 34+ scrapers now work (not just PirateBay) - base class urllib migration complete
- Fixed: Trakt API - real CLIENT_ID and CLIENT_SECRET for proper OAuth
- Fixed: Trakt lists/menus hardened for all response formats (Trending/Popular/Watchlist/Collection)
- Fixed: Trakt list items now pass TMDB IDs for metadata
- Removed: script.module.requests and script.module.six dependencies

v2.1.4 (2026)
- Fixed: Debrid container refresh on authorisation.

v2.1.3 (2026)
- Fixed: AllDebrid authorisation.

v2.1.2 (2026)
- Fixed: Busy spinner on playback.

v2.1.1 (2026)
- Fixed: Replaced setResolvedUrl with xbmc.Player().play() to prevent rescrape loop
- Fixed: Trakt API now uses native urllib (no more requests dependency crash)
- Added: Custom source dialog showing source/scraper count and quality breakdown
- Added: Up Next - auto-play next episode for TV series
- Added: Skip Intro prompt during first 90 seconds of TV episodes
- Removed: repository.gujal from repo

v2.1.0 (2026)
- Added 34+ scrapers including Russian, Chinese, Anime sources
- Fixed TMDB integration with native urllib

v2.0.0 (2026)
- Complete rewrite for Kodi 21+ (Python 3)
- Added modern torrent scrapers
- Added Jackett integration
- Added Real-Debrid, Premiumize, AllDebrid support
        </news>
        <assets>
            <icon>icon.png</icon>
            <fanart>fanart.jpg</fanart>
        </assets>
    </extension>
</addon>
