<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<addon id="plugin.video.salts" version="2.9.69" name="SALTS - Stream All The Sources" provider-name="tknorris, Zeus768">
    <requires>
        <import addon="xbmc.python" version="3.0.0"/>
        <import addon="script.module.resolveurl" version="5.1.0"/>
        <import addon="script.module.beautifulsoup4" version="4.9.0"/>
        <import addon="script.module.salts_scrapers" version="1.0.4"/>
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource" library="default.py">
        <provides>video</provides>
    </extension>
    <extension point="xbmc.service" library="service.py" start="startup"/>
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
        <summary lang="en_GB">Stream All The Sources - 120+ scrapers, Stremio, Trakt, Debrid, Live Movie Channels</summary>
        <description lang="en_GB">SALTS is a multi-source video addon with 120+ scrapers providing maximum coverage for movies and TV shows

NOTE (v2.9.21): All scrapers now live in a separate Kodi script module,
"Salts Scrapers - Scrape All The Sources" (script.module.salts_scrapers),
authored by Zeus768. It is auto-installed as a dependency.</description>
        <platform>all</platform>
        <license>GPL-3.0-only</license>
        <website>https://github.com/zeus768/plugin.video.salts</website>
        <source>https://github.com/zeus768/plugin.video.salts</source>
        <news>
v2.9.69 (2026-05) - TORBOX FINAL FIX - STOPPED REPEATED API CALLS
|- Fixed: The ACTUAL root cause - Kodi was calling torbox_play_file() multiple
|||  times (4 calls in 18 seconds) because I was using player.play() instead of
|||  xbmcplugin.setResolvedUrl(). Each retry made a NEW TorBox API request,
|||  causing API spam that eventually kicked the stream out.
|||  
|||  THE REAL ISSUE ALL ALONG:
|||  - Using player.play() with plugin:// URLs causes Kodi to retry on failure
|||  - Each retry calls torbox_play_file() AGAIN
|||  - Each call makes a NEW requestdl API call to TorBox
|||  - Multiple rapid API calls → TorBox rate limits/kicks stream
|||  
|||  v2.9.69 Solution:
|||  1. Changed from player.play() to xbmcplugin.setResolvedUrl()
|||  2. setResolvedUrl tells Kodi "here's the final URL, stop calling me"
|||  3. Function only called ONCE, not 4+ times
|||  4. Single TorBox API request instead of spam
|||  5. Stream plays smoothly without repeated loading attempts
|||  
|||  This was the issue from the very first report - stream would start playing
|||  but then keep trying to load and eventually fail. Now fixed properly.
|||
v2.9.68 (2026-05) - TORBOX CODEC FIX - REMOVED ALL HEADERS
|- Fixed: "CVideoPlayerVideo::OpenStream - could not open video codec" error.
|||  v2.9.67 was adding headers using pipe syntax (URL|User-Agent=...) which was
|||  preventing the video codec from opening properly. Kodi couldn't parse the
|||  URL format correctly, causing immediate playback failure.
|||  
|||  ROOT CAUSE FOUND: Headers in pipe format break FFmpeg's video codec initialization.
|||  
|||  v2.9.68 Changes:
|||  1. REMOVED ALL headers from URL (no pipe syntax)
|||  2. Using CLEAN TorBox URL only
|||  3. Let Kodi/FFmpeg handle the connection natively
|||  4. Simplified torbox_play_file() function completely
|||  
|||  TorBox URLs work WITHOUT custom headers - they don't need User-Agent.
|||  The previous failures were caused by my header additions, not lack of headers.
|||
v2.9.67 (2026-05) - TORBOX PLAYBACK FIX - REMOVED INCOMPATIBLE INPUTSTREAM SETTINGS
|- Fixed: TorBox streams now play immediately without long timeouts or failures.
|||  v2.9.66 was forcing inputstream.adaptive with HLS manifest type, but TorBox
|||  serves DIRECT MKV/MP4 files, not HLS streams. This mismatch caused Kodi to
|||  wait ~80 seconds trying to parse the file as HLS before failing with
|||  "Playlist Player: skipping unplayable item".
|||  
|||  Changes in v2.9.67:
|||  1. REMOVED inputstream.adaptive force (let Kodi auto-detect stream type)
|||  2. REMOVED HLS manifest_type setting (not applicable to direct files)
|||  3. REMOVED application/vnd.apple.mpegurl MIME type
|||  4. Simplified headers to just User-Agent (all that's needed)
|||  5. Kodi now correctly handles MKV/MP4 files with native FFmpeg
|||
|||  All other v2.9.66 fixes retained:
|||  - Fresh URL requests (no caching)
|||  - Retry logic with exponential backoff
|||  - Monitor pause during playback
|||

        </news>
        <assets>
            <icon>icon.png</icon>
            <fanart>fanart.jpg</fanart>
        </assets>
    </extension>
</addon>
