<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<addon id="plugin.video.salts" version="2.6.1" name="SALTS - Stream All The Sources" provider-name="tknorris, zeus768">
    <requires>
        <import addon="xbmc.python" version="3.0.0"/>
        <import addon="script.module.resolveurl" version="5.1.0"/>
        <import addon="script.module.beautifulsoup4" version="4.9.0"/>
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource" library="default.py">
        <provides>video</provides>
    </extension>
    <extension point="xbmc.service" library="service.py" start="startup"/>
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
        <summary lang="en_GB">Stream All The Sources - 45+ scrapers, Stremio, Trakt, Debrid</summary>
        <description lang="en_GB">SALTS is a multi-source video addon with 45+ scrapers including Stremio protocol (Torrentio, MediaFusion, Comet, CyberFlix, PeerFlix).

Features:
- Stremio Scrapers: Torrentio, MediaFusion, Comet, CyberFlix (free), Annatar, PeerFlix (free), EasyNews+
- Torrent Sites: 1337x, YTS, EZTV, TorrentGalaxy, TPB, NNM-Club, RuTracker, RuTor, Nyaa, etc.
- Free Streams: VidSrc, 2Embed, AutoEmbed, CyberFlix, PeerFlix (no debrid needed)
- Jackett/Prowlarr Integration: Connect to any indexer
- Debrid Services: Real-Debrid, Premiumize, AllDebrid, TorBox
- Trakt.tv: Scrobbling, mark watched, watchlists, collections, history with TMDB posters
- ResolveURL for 270+ hosting sites

Revived and modernized by zeus768 for Kodi 21 Omega and above.
Original author: tknorris
Thank you to Mister X and Zaxxon709</description>
        <platform>all</platform>
        <license>GPL-3.0-only</license>
        <website>https://github.com/zeus768/plugin.video.salts</website>
        <source>https://github.com/zeus768/plugin.video.salts</source>
        <news>
v2.6.0 (2026)
- Added: Torrentio scraper (Stremio protocol) - 20+ torrent indexers aggregated
- Added: MediaFusion scraper (Stremio protocol) - community torrent/stream aggregator
- Added: Comet scraper (Stremio protocol) - fast torrent aggregator
- Added: CyberFlix scraper (Stremio, FREE) - direct streams, no debrid required
- Added: Annatar scraper (Stremio protocol) - Jackett/Prowlarr via Stremio
- Added: PeerFlix scraper (Stremio, FREE) - P2P streams, no debrid required
- Added: EasyNews+ scraper (Stremio protocol) - Usenet streams
- Fixed: Trakt scrobbling now fires during playback (start at 2%, stop on finish)
- Fixed: Trakt mark watched - items marked after 80% playback completion
- Fixed: Trakt lists now show TMDB posters, fanart, ratings, and watched overlay
- Fixed: Trakt stale ADDON instance bug - fresh xbmcaddon.Addon() for all settings reads/writes
- Fixed: Watched tick indicator ([W]) on Trakt list items with playcount overlay

v2.5.3 (2026)
- User's custom fixes and improvements

v2.1.8 (2026)
- Fixed: Source dialog rendering - moved to inline native Kodi Dialog().select() with color-coded formatting
- Fixed: Eliminated external module dependency for source dialog (no more import failures)
- Added: Quality color badges inline (gold 4K, green 1080p, blue 720p, purple 480p, gray SD)
- Added: CACHED/FREE tags, seed health coloring, file sizes all in native dialog

v2.1.7 (2026)
- Added: Bento UI Source Dialog - custom skin with quality-colored badges, cached/free tags, seeds, size
- Added: Pre-Scrape hover caching - background scrape after 2s hover on movie items (4-link rule)
- Added: 24hr TTL hover cache in SQLite for instant source availability
        </news>
        <assets>
            <icon>icon.png</icon>
            <fanart>fanart.jpg</fanart>
        </assets>
    </extension>
</addon>
