<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<addon id="plugin.video.salts" version="2.8.0" name="SALTS - Stream All The Sources" provider-name="tknorris, zeus768">
    <requires>
        <import addon="xbmc.python" version="3.0.0"/>
        <import addon="script.module.resolveurl" version="5.1.0"/>
        <import addon="script.module.beautifulsoup4" version="4.9.0"/>
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource" library="default.py">
        <provides>video</provides>
    </extension>
    <extension point="xbmc.service" library="service.py" start="startup"/>
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
        <summary lang="en_GB">Stream All The Sources - 120+ scrapers, Stremio, Trakt, Debrid, Live Movie Channels</summary>
        <description lang="en_GB">SALTS is a multi-source video addon with 120+ scrapers providing maximum coverage for movies and TV shows.

=== FREE STREAMS (No Debrid Required) ===
- VidSrc Network: VidSrc.xyz, VidSrc.cc, VidSrc.in, VidSrc.pm, VidSrc.nl, VidSrc.pro, VidSrc.me, VidSrc.to
- Embed Services: 2Embed, Embed.su, AutoEmbed, MultiEmbed, VidLink, VidPlay, MoviesAPI, SmashyStream
- Streaming Sites: FlixHQ, BFlix, HDToday, Soap2Day, LookMovie, FMovies, 123Movies, MoviesJoy, Putlocker
- And 40+ more free streaming sources!

=== STREMIO FREE ADDONS ===
- Braflix, StreamingCommunity, TheMovieArchive, PublicDomainMovies
- KnightCrawler, Jackettio, AIOStreams, Torrentio (Free Mode)
- PlutoTV, Tubi, and more!

=== TORRENT SITES ===
- Primary: 1337x, YTS, EZTV, TorrentGalaxy, ThePirateBay, SolidTorrents
- Secondary: LimeTorrents, Torrentz2, RARBG, Kickass, MagnetDL, iDope
- Additional: BitSearch, TorLock, TorrentFunk, TorrentsCSV, and more!

=== ANIME ===
- Zoro, 9Anime, GogoAnime, AniWave, HiAnime, AnimePahe
- Nyaa, SubsPlease, AnimeTosho, and more!

=== ASIAN DRAMA ===
- WatchAsian, KissAsian, DramaCool, ViewAsian, AsianLoad

=== INTERNATIONAL ===
- Russian: RuTracker, RuTor, NNM-Club
- Chinese: DyTT, BTBTT
- French: Torrent9, YggTorrent

=== STREMIO DEBRID SCRAPERS ===
- Torrentio, MediaFusion, Comet, CyberFlix, Annatar, PeerFlix, EasyNews+

=== FEATURES ===
- Live Movie Channels with EPG (35+ channels)
- Episode Countdown Tracker
- Network Browser (Netflix, HBO, BBC, etc.)
- Returning Shows (New Seasons)
- AI-Powered Natural Language Search
- Trakt Integration with Scrobbling
- Debrid Services: Real-Debrid, Premiumize, AllDebrid, TorBox
- Jackett/Prowlarr Integration
- Pre-scrape on Hover
- Source Caching

Revived and massively expanded by zeus768 for Kodi 21 Omega and above.
Original author: tknorris
Thank you to Mister X and Zaxxon709</description>
        <platform>all</platform>
        <license>GPL-3.0-only</license>
        <website>https://github.com/zeus768/plugin.video.salts</website>
        <source>https://github.com/zeus768/plugin.video.salts</source>
        <news>
v2.8.0 (2026-01-15) - MASSIVE SCRAPER EXPANSION
- Added: 75+ NEW SCRAPERS bringing total to 120+ sources!
- Added: VidSrc Network (8 mirrors): xyz, cc, in, pm, nl, pro, me, to
- Added: 2Embed variants, Embed.su, AutoEmbed, MultiEmbed, VidLink, VidPlay
- Added: MoviesAPI, SmashyStream, NontonGo, RgShorts/RiveStream
- Added: Stremio Free Addons: Braflix, StreamingCommunity, TheMovieArchive, PublicDomainMovies
- Added: KnightCrawler, Jackettio, Orionoid, TPBPlus, AIOStreams, StremThru, MediaFlow
- Added: Torrentio Free Mode, PlutoTV, Tubi integration
- Added: 20+ Streaming Sites: FlixHQ, BFlix, HDToday, Soap2Day, LookMovie, FMovies, etc.
- Added: Additional Torrents: BitSearch, TorLock, TorrentFunk, TorrentsCSV, YggTorrent, Torrent9
- Added: 12+ Anime Sources: Zoro, 9Anime, GogoAnime, AniWave, HiAnime, AnimePahe, etc.
- Added: Asian Drama: WatchAsian, KissAsian, DramaCool, ViewAsian, AsianLoad
- Improved: Settings organized by category for easier management
- Improved: Source discovery with parallel scraping support

v2.7.2 (2026-01-12)
- Added: Movie Schedules - View what's playing on all movie channels for the next 12 hours
- Added: Force Refresh EPG button in Movie Channels menu
- Added: Returning Shows - Browse TV shows with new seasons starting in next 30 days
- Added: Network Browser - Browse TV shows by network (Netflix, HBO, BBC, Amazon, Disney+, Apple TV+, and 20+ more)
- Added: Episode Countdown - Track your favorite shows and see days until next episode
- Added: Context menu "Track Episode Countdown" on all TV shows
- Added: TODAY/TOMORROW/X days countdown indicators
- Improved: EPG now shows unique movies per channel based on genre

v2.7.1 (2026-01-12)
- Fixed: EPG now shows unique movies for each channel (no more duplicate listings)
- Fixed: Each movie channel pulls from TMDB based on genre (Action, Comedy, Thriller, etc.)
- Added: Channel logos/icons for all 35+ movie channels
- Added: New Preferences settings category
- Added: "Show International Premieres" setting - toggle Japanese, Chinese, Korean shows
- Changed: Latest Show Premieres now defaults to English/American shows only
- Added: Country indicators on international show premieres when enabled

v2.7.0 (2026-01-10)
- Added: Live Movie Channels with EPG support (35+ channels worldwide)
- Added: EPG integration showing current and next programs
- Added: Watch Live or Start from Beginning choice for channels
- Added: New Episodes Today calendar (scroll back up to 7 days)
- Added: Latest Show Premieres with infinite pagination (50 items/page, last 7 days)
- Added: Smart movie stream finding when clicking on live channels
        </news>
        <assets>
            <icon>icon.png</icon>
            <fanart>fanart.jpg</fanart>
        </assets>
    </extension>
</addon>
