<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<addon id="plugin.video.trakt_player" name="Trakt Player" version="2.3.0" provider-name="zeus768">
    <requires>
        <import addon="xbmc.python" version="3.0.0"/>
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource" library="main.py">
        <provides>video</provides>
    </extension>
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
        <summary lang="en">Superpowered Trakt Player - Click and Play with Debrid, AI Vibes, Discovery Feed</summary>
        <description lang="en">Full Trakt and TMDB integration for Movies and TV Shows. Click-and-Play via Debrid services (Real-Debrid, AllDebrid, Premiumize). AI-powered discovery, trailer feed, and marathon mode.

Features:
- Click-and-Play: Auto 1080p via debrid with cache-first priority
- AI Vibes: Mood-based movie marathons powered by AI
- Discovery Feed: Trending/upcoming trailers with marathon mode
- Trakt Superpowers: Recommendations, Calendar, Continue Watching, Friends, Stats
- Debrid: Real-Debrid, AllDebrid, Premiumize with file-based token storage
- Scrobble: Automatic Trakt scrobbling during playback
- Up Next: Auto-play next episode
- Custom Lists: Create, browse, and manage Trakt lists

Created by zeus768.

CHANGELOG:

v2.2.0 - Feature Merge + Premiumize Fix
- MERGED: All custom features into zeus768's v2.1.6 fixed build
- FIXED: Premiumize device code auth (was hitting /api/token instead of /token)
- ADDED: AI Vibes - mood-based discovery with 12 presets + custom
- ADDED: Discovery Feed - trending trailers, new releases, upcoming, shuffle, marathon
- ADDED: Continue Watching from Trakt playback progress
- ADDED: Recommended For You (personalized Trakt recommendations)
- ADDED: Anticipated movies/shows
- ADDED: My Calendar (upcoming episodes)
- ADDED: My Custom Lists (create, browse, manage)
- ADDED: Popular Community Lists
- ADDED: Friends activity feed
- ADDED: User Stats dashboard
- ADDED: Account Status (debrid expiry, premium status)
- ADDED: Buy Me a Beer (Ko-fi QR code)
- ADDED: Rate on Trakt, Add to Watchlist, Add to List

v2.1.6 - Speed Optimizations
- FASTER: Trakt lists now load 3-5x faster with parallel TMDB image fetching
- FASTER: Reduced items per page to 30 for quicker loading
- FASTER: Added image caching to avoid re-fetching
- FASTER: Reduced API timeouts for snappier response

v2.1.5 - Major Fixes
- FIXED: Trakt and Debrid authorization now persists properly
- FIXED: Uses file-based token storage (trakt_token.json, rd_token.json)
- FIXED: Auto-play with proper quality fallback (1080p to 720p to 480p)
- FIXED: Cached torrent detection and priority playback
- ADDED: Unlimited scroll/pagination in all lists
- ADDED: Addon icon and fanart in all subfolders

v1.0.8 - Initial Release
- Trakt and Debrid authorization using native urllib</description>
        <disclaimer lang="en">This addon does not host any content.</disclaimer>
        <language>en</language>
        <platform>all</platform>
        <license>GPL-2.0-only</license>
        <news>
v2.3.0 (2026)
- FIXED: Premiumize auth code not showing (was sending grant_type instead of response_type)
- FIXED: Real-Debrid false "expired" errors (token refresh now falls back to testing current token)
- ADDED: Real account info for all debrid services (username, email, expiry date, days left)
- ADDED: Real-Debrid shows fidelity points
- ADDED: Color-coded expiry warnings (green/yellow/red based on days left)
- IMPROVED: Account Status page now fetches live data from RD/PM/AD APIs

v2.2.0 (2026)
- FIXED: Premiumize device code auth (was hitting /api/token instead of /token)
- MERGED: All custom features into zeus768's v2.1.6 fixed build
- ADDED: AI Vibes, Discovery Feed, Continue Watching, Recommendations
- ADDED: Calendar, Custom Lists, Popular Lists, Friends, Stats
- ADDED: Account Status, Buy Me a Beer, Rate, Watchlist, Add to List

v2.1.6 (2026)
- FASTER: Trakt lists 3-5x faster with parallel TMDB image fetching
- FASTER: Image caching, reduced API timeouts

v2.1.5 (2026)
- FIXED: Trakt/Debrid auth persistence (file-based token storage)
- ADDED: Unlimited pagination, quality fallback playback
        </news>
        <assets>
            <icon>icon.png</icon>
            <fanart>fanart.jpg</fanart>
        </assets>
    </extension>
</addon>
