<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<addon id="plugin.video.trakt_player" name="Trakt Player" version="2.4.5" provider-name="zeus768">
    <requires>
        <import addon="xbmc.python" version="3.0.0"/>
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource" library="main.py">
        <provides>video</provides>
    </extension>
    <extension point="xbmc.service" library="service.py" start="startup"/>
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
        <summary lang="en">Superpowered Trakt Player - Click and Play with Debrid, AI Vibes, Discovery Feed</summary>
        <description lang="en">Trakt Player v2.3.0 - Click-and-Play via 5 Debrid services (Real-Debrid, AllDebrid, Premiumize, TorBox, LinkSnappy). Real account info with expiry tracking. AI Vibes, Discovery Feed, Trakt Scrobbling, Recommendations, Calendar, Friends, Stats, Custom Lists. Created by zeus768.

Features:
- Click-and-Play: Auto 1080p via debrid with cache-first priority
- AI Vibes: Mood-based movie marathons powered by AI
- Discovery Feed: Trending/upcoming trailers with marathon mode
- Trakt Superpowers: Recommendations, Calendar, Continue Watching, Friends, Stats
- Debrid: Real-Debrid, AllDebrid, Premiumize with file-based token storage
- Scrobble: Automatic Trakt scrobbling during playback
- Up Next: Auto-play next episode
- Custom Lists: Create, browse, and manage Trakt lists

Created by zeus768.

CHANGELOG:

v2.2.0 - Feature Merge + Premiumize Fix
- MERGED: All custom features into zeus768's v2.1.6 fixed build
- FIXED: Premiumize device code auth (was hitting /api/token instead of /token)
- ADDED: AI Vibes - mood-based discovery with 12 presets + custom
- ADDED: Discovery Feed - trending trailers, new releases, upcoming, shuffle, marathon
- ADDED: Continue Watching from Trakt playback progress
- ADDED: Recommended For You (personalized Trakt recommendations)
- ADDED: Anticipated movies/shows
- ADDED: My Calendar (upcoming episodes)
- ADDED: My Custom Lists (create, browse, manage)
- ADDED: Popular Community Lists
- ADDED: Friends activity feed
- ADDED: User Stats dashboard
- ADDED: Account Status (debrid expiry, premium status)
- ADDED: Buy Me a Beer (Ko-fi QR code)
- ADDED: Rate on Trakt, Add to Watchlist, Add to List

v2.1.6 - Speed Optimizations
- FASTER: Trakt lists now load 3-5x faster with parallel TMDB image fetching
- FASTER: Reduced items per page to 30 for quicker loading
- FASTER: Added image caching to avoid re-fetching
- FASTER: Reduced API timeouts for snappier response

v2.1.5 - Major Fixes
- FIXED: Trakt and Debrid authorization now persists properly
- FIXED: Uses file-based token storage (trakt_token.json, rd_token.json)
- FIXED: Auto-play with proper quality fallback (1080p to 720p to 480p)
- FIXED: Cached torrent detection and priority playback
- ADDED: Unlimited scroll/pagination in all lists
- ADDED: Addon icon and fanart in all subfolders

v1.0.8 - Initial Release
- Trakt and Debrid authorization using native urllib</description>
        <disclaimer lang="en">This addon does not host any content.</disclaimer>
        <language>en</language>
        <platform>all</platform>
        <license>GPL-2.0-only</license>
        <news>
v2.4.3 (2026)
- FIXED: Wrong posters in mixed Trakt lists (watchlists, popular lists,
  custom lists, history, friend activity, continue watching).
  * Each item's actual type (movie/show/episode) is now detected from
    Trakt's own 'type' field instead of a hard-coded default.
  * Posters now fetched from the correct TMDB namespace (movie vs tv),
    fixing random/unrelated artwork being shown for TV shows.
  * Episode entries (history, playback progress) now correctly use the
    parent show's poster.
  * Image batch limit increased from 30 to 100 so long lists also get
    posters for every item.

v2.4.2 (2026)
- NEW: 1337x Scraper - reliable torrent source with multiple mirrors
- NEW: Debrid Cloud Browser - browse and play files from your debrid cloud
  * Real-Debrid: View torrents, files, download history
  * Premiumize: Browse cloud files and folders, view transfers
  * Torbox: View torrents and files
  * AllDebrid: Browse magnets and files
- Delete items from cloud via context menu
- Direct playback from cloud without re-searching

v2.4.1 (2026)
- FIXED: Critical playback bug - added missing extract_hash() function
- Links now resolve and play correctly via debrid services
- Hash extraction supports both hex (40-char) and base32 (32-char) formats

v2.4.0 (2026)
- NEW: Episode Notifications - Get alerts when new episodes drop for your watchlist shows
- NEW: Pre-Cache Next Episode - Auto-adds next episode to debrid while watching
- Background service for notifications and pre-cache monitoring
- New settings categories for notifications and pre-cache options

v2.3.1 (2026)
- FIXED: Premiumize authorization (ported working OAuth flow from v2.1.8)
- FIXED: Torbox authorization (ported working device code auth from v2.1.8)

v2.3.0 (2026)
- FIXED: Real-Debrid false "expired" errors (token refresh fallback)
- ADDED: TorBox debrid (device code auth, cache check, magnet resolve)
- ADDED: LinkSnappy debrid (login auth, 30+ file host link generation)
- ADDED: Real account info for all 5 debrid services (RD/AD/PM/TB/LS)
- Color-coded expiry warnings on Account Status page

v2.2.0 (2026)
- FIXED: Premiumize device code auth (was hitting /api/token instead of /token)
- MERGED: All custom features into zeus768's v2.1.6 fixed build
- ADDED: AI Vibes, Discovery Feed, Continue Watching, Recommendations
- ADDED: Calendar, Custom Lists, Popular Lists, Friends, Stats
- ADDED: Account Status, Buy Me a Beer, Rate, Watchlist, Add to List

v2.1.6 (2026)
- FASTER: Trakt lists 3-5x faster with parallel TMDB image fetching
- FASTER: Image caching, reduced API timeouts

v2.1.5 (2026)
- FIXED: Trakt/Debrid auth persistence (file-based token storage)
- ADDED: Unlimited pagination, quality fallback playback
        </news>
        <assets>
            <icon>icon.png</icon>
            <fanart>fanart.jpg</fanart>
        </assets>
    </extension>
</addon>
