<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<addon id="plugin.video.genesis" name="Genesis" version="9.4.0" provider-name="zeus768">
    <requires>
        <import addon="xbmc.python" version="3.0.0" />
        <import addon="script.genesis.media" version="9.2.4" />
        <import addon="script.module.cocoscrapers" optional="true" />
        <import addon="script.module.gears" optional="true" />
        <import addon="script.module.requests" optional="true" />
        <import addon="plugin.video.youtube" optional="true" />
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource" library="default.py">
        <provides>video</provides>
    </extension>
    <extension point="xbmc.service" library="service.py" start="startup" />
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
        <summary lang="en">Genesis - Stream Movies and TV Shows with Debrid, Trakt, CocoScrapers, Gears</summary>
        <description lang="en">Genesis - Your ultimate streaming addon for Movies and TV Shows. Torrent and streaming scrapers with debrid support (Real-Debrid, Premiumize, AllDebrid, TorBox). External scraper support for CocoScrapers and Gears Scrapers modules. Full Trakt.tv integration. Fully compatible with Kodi 21 Omega and above (Python 3).

Features:
- Built-in scrapers: Meteor, Streamthru, Torz, Webstreamr
- Torrent scrapers: 1337x, YTS, EZTV, TorrentGalaxy, ThePirateBay
- External scrapers: CocoScrapers, Gears Scrapers (install separately)
- Debrid: Real-Debrid, Premiumize, AllDebrid, TorBox
- Trakt.tv: Auth, watchlists, collections, progress, history
- TMDB metadata, poster art, genre browsing
- Multiple skins/themes via Genesis Themepak
- Autoplay and resume playback</description>
        <disclaimer lang="en">The author does not host or distribute any of the content displayed by this addon. The author does not have any affiliation with the content provider.</disclaimer>
        <platform>all</platform>
        <news>
v9.4.0 (2026)
- FIXED: All movie/TV categories now load properly (migrated from broken IMDB scraping to Trakt API)
- FIXED: Metadata enrichment migrated from dead OMDB to TMDB API (posters, cast, directors, plot)
- FIXED: Genre browsing uses correct Trakt genre slugs (science-fiction, superhero, etc.)
- FIXED: All Trakt API URLs updated to api.trakt.tv (HTTPS)
- ADDED: TMDB poster/fanart/backdrop artwork for all movies and TV shows
- ADDED: Full cast and director info from TMDB credits API
- ADDED: Updated TV Networks list (Disney+, Apple TV+, Paramount+, Peacock, Hulu)
- ADDED: TMDB-powered person search and popular actors browsing

v9.3.0 (2026)
- FIXED: Python 3 / Kodi 21 compatibility across ALL files
- FIXED: Trakt auth URL updated from api-v2launch.trakt.tv to api.trakt.tv (HTTPS)
- FIXED: All debrid resolvers (RD, PM, AD, TorBox) Python 3 imports
- ADDED: CocoScrapers and Gears Scrapers external provider support

v9.2.6 (2026)
- User's fixed build for Kodi 21
- Meteor, Streamthru, Torz, Webstreamr scrapers
        </news>
        <assets>
            <icon>icon.png</icon>
            <fanart>fanart.jpg</fanart>
        </assets>
    </extension>
</addon>
