<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<addon id="plugin.video.vidscr"
       name="Vidscr"
       version="1.4.15"
       provider-name="Zeus768">
    <requires>
        <import addon="xbmc.python" version="3.0.0"/>
        <import addon="script.module.requests" version="2.22.0"/>
        <import addon="script.module.resolveurl" version="5.1.0" optional="true"/>
        <import addon="inputstream.adaptive" version="2.0.0" optional="true"/>
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource" library="default.py">
        <provides>video</provides>
    </extension>
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
        <reuselanguageinvoker>true</reuselanguageinvoker>
        <summary lang="en_GB">Vidscr — Movies &amp; TV via TMDB + Vidsrc (by Zeus768)</summary>
        <description lang="en_GB">A clean, simple Movies &amp; TV Shows addon. Browse new releases, Oscar nominees, genres, actors, networks and a 7-day premiering calendar. Posters and metadata from TMDB; streams sourced from vidsrcme.ru (with optional vidsrc.xyz / 2embed secondary), built-in resolvers, server sub-picker, per-show quality memory, Trakt scrobbling, watched/resume indicators and 10-second stall auto-fallback.</description>
        <platform>all</platform>
        <license>GPL-3.0-or-later</license>
        <assets>
            <icon>icon.png</icon>
            <fanart>fanart.jpg</fanart>
        <news>v1.4.15 — DEPENDENCY FIX: v1.4.14 declared script.module.pycryptodome as an optional dependency, but some Kodi builds (notably the Android one without a populated repo) blocked install with "Dependency unresolved on script.module.pycryptodome". v1.4.15 removes the external pycryptodome dependency entirely and embeds a PURE-PYTHON implementation of AES-256-GCM and ChaCha20-Poly1305 (resources/lib/purecrypto.py) — verified against NIST AES-GCM and RFC 7539 ChaCha20-Poly1305 test vectors. Stigstream now works on every Kodi install regardless of which crypto modules are present. Order tried: pycryptodome (fastest, if available) → pyca/cryptography → embedded pure-Python (slow but always works).</news>


        </assets>
        <news>v1.4.14 — NEW SOURCE: Stigstream (stigstream.ru). Reverse-engineered the site's doubly-encrypted JSON API (outer AES-256-GCM, inner ChaCha20-Poly1305, both keyed via HKDF-SHA512 from a 32-byte master extracted from the public JS bundle), then queries 8 of its regional servers (Aqua, Nova, Vix, Nebula, Quartz, Obsidian, Onyx, Atlas) IN PARALLEL and merges every working stream into the source list. Each server returns a clean HLS m3u8 URL through the site's CORS proxy at proxy.stigstream.ru — directly playable, no JS execution required. Independent CDN (tik.1x2.space and friends), so titles cloudnestra doesn't carry have a real second chance. Verified working on titles that previously returned 0 streams (Dark Knight tt0468569, etc.). Toggle: Settings → Sources → "Enable Stigstream source" (on by default). Requires script.module.pycryptodome OR Python's cryptography package — pycryptodome is added as an OPTIONAL dependency; it's already present on most Kodi installs because ResolveURL pulls it in.</news>


        <news>v1.4.13 — DUMP-OVERWRITE FIX: in v1.4.10-12 the cloudnestra body dump filename was just ``cloudnestra_dump_YYYYMMDD-HHMMSS.json`` so when 6 servers tried at the same second they all overwrote each other and the user ended up exporting only the LAST attempt — usually a useless 281-byte 404 page. v1.4.13 now suffixes each filename with an md5 hash of the rcp URL plus ``_NEXTOK`` (next-hop body captured) or ``_NONEXT`` (next-hop missing). The retention policy now preferentially keeps ``_NEXTOK`` dumps because those are the ones that actually contain the prorcp body we need to decode. Also: when the prorcp body is short (≤5000 chars), it is now logged inline in vidscr_debug.log so it can be inspected without exporting the dump folder.</news>


        <news>v1.4.12 — THE REAL FIX (cloudnestra "no streams"): cloudnestra was responding with content-encoding: br (Brotli compression). Kodi's bundled Python on Android does NOT ship the brotli module — so requests was returning ~200 bytes of binary garbage instead of the 4-5 KB HTML, _find_next_hop couldn't extract the prorcp link, every server returned 0 candidates. The fix: stop advertising Brotli in Accept-Encoding (gzip+deflate are honoured by cloudnestra and natively decoded by Python's stdlib). Applied to vidsrc.py, vidsrc2.py, and the _BROWSER_HEADERS used for Cloudflare-challenged retries. Also: cloudnestra body dumps now include a base64-encoded raw-bytes copy for binary-safe inspection.</news>


        <news>v1.4.11 — CRITICAL FIX: stale Python bytecode cache (.pyc) on Android meant Kodi was running v1.4.9 code even after install-from-zip put v1.4.10 .py files in place — so v1.4.10's regex fix and cloudnestra body auto-capture never actually ran. v1.4.11 adds a version-stamped pyc invalidator at the very top of default.py: on every addon-version change, EVERY ``__pycache__`` directory and orphan .pyc inside the addon is wiped before any addon module is imported, guaranteeing the new code loads. (Symptoms this fixes: "no such group" errors after upgrade; missing new log lines; "appearing to do nothing" after install.)

v1.4.10 — FIX (vidsrc.icu regex regression from v1.4.9): the alternation in the rcp-extraction pattern was non-capturing, causing every vidsrc.icu auto-fallback attempt to crash with "no such group". Wrapped the alternation in a capturing group. NEW (Cloudnestra resolver): broader stream-URL detection — searches inside every inline &lt;script&gt; tag, decodes any 60+ char base64 blob looking for embedded m3u8 URLs, and adds new patterns for hls/playlist/manifest/playlistUrl JSON keys plus unicode-escaped URLs. NEW (Auto-capture): when cloudnestra returns a body that yields no stream candidates, the addon now writes the FULL prorcp body to ``profile/cloudnestra_dumps/cloudnestra_dump_*.json``. NEW: Settings → Debug → "Export captured cloudnestra body dumps to Downloads" action copies these dumps to your Downloads folder for analysis. Keeps only the 5 most recent dumps.

v1.4.9 — FIX (Sources regression): the v1.4.8 attempt to add JSON-API resolvers (vidsrc.icu / vidlink.pro / vidjoy.pro) was based on outdated public docs — those endpoints all return 404. Removed. ALSO fixed the host-routing regression where ``sources.py`` overrode ``secondary_source_host`` on a fresh ``xbmcaddon.Addon()`` instance but ``vidsrc2._host()`` reads from the module-level ``common.ADDON`` singleton — meaning every host in the auto-fallback chain was actually hitting whatever was last saved (e.g. vidsrc.to) instead of the host requested. The host is now passed as an explicit parameter to ``vidsrc2.resolve_all``. NEW: vidsrc.icu inner-iframe scraping — its ``/embed/movie/{id}`` page wraps a vidsrcme.vidsrc.icu iframe whose body contains real cloudnestra rcp URLs that the primary resolver can chase.

IMPORTANT NOTE — Most public free streaming proxies (cloudnestra, vidsrc.cc, vidsrc.to, embed.su, autoembed, smashy, etc.) have moved to JavaScript-based player loaders + Cloudflare fingerprint challenges in 2026 that static HTTP scrapers cannot defeat. Streams may still fail to resolve regardless of how clever the upstream URL detection is. This is an ecosystem-wide change affecting every free-scraper Kodi addon — the realistic alternatives in 2026 are: a Real-Debrid / Premiumize / AllDebrid integration; a self-hosted JS-executing resolver (Playwright/Puppeteer); or sticking to community-maintained scrapers with paid services attached.

v1.4.8 — FIX (Trakt / SIMKL / Bingebase OAuth): "Authorises but token is never saved" — token is now persisted to BOTH the addon settings (primary) and the local JSON file (backup) for ALL THREE trackers. Detailed logging at every step of the device-code / PIN flow makes it obvious where authentication fails. HTTP 409 ("code already used") is now handled. New "Show * token status" debug actions under Settings → Trakt / SIMKL / Bingebase confirm exactly what is stored, where, and whether is_authenticated() returns True. After successful authentication the corresponding *_enabled flag is auto-toggled on so scrobbling works immediately.

v1.4.7 — NEW (Debug): in-depth diagnostic report — Settings → Debug → "Run deep diagnostic report" audits system + Kodi + dependencies + writable paths, probes every stream host (TMDB, vidsrcme.ru, vidsrc.xyz/to/net/cc, 2embed, embed.su, multiembed, autoembed, moviesapi, smashy, cloudnestra, Trakt, SIMKL, gofile) with timings/HTTP status, and dumps every addon setting with secrets auto-redacted. NEW: "Probe all stream hosts" quick reachability test. NEW: "Export debug bundle (.zip)" saves diagnostic_report.txt + vidscr_debug.log + settings_redacted.json + environment.json to the device Downloads folder. NEW (Device bundle): "Download addon zip to Downloads folder" works on every device — Android / Fire TV / Nvidia Shield / Windows / macOS / Linux / iOS / tvOS — with automatic Downloads folder detection (probes /storage/emulated/0/Download, ~/Downloads, special://home/Downloads, LibreELEC /storage/downloads and more). NEW: optional "Upload addon zip to gofile.io" → shareable link for cross-device sideloading. NEW: "Custom Downloads folder" setting for locked-down devices. NEW: "Show resolved Downloads folder" action so you can see exactly where the zip will land. All secrets (TMDB key, Trakt/SIMKL/Bingebase tokens) are redacted from every diagnostic output.

v1.4.6 — FIX: "No streams available" caused by cloudnestra page format changes & ResolveURL-only secondary chain. Resolver now: (1) recognises ~10 next-hop patterns (data-h XOR cipher, JS-set iframe.src, atob-decoded prorcp, document.write iframes, location.replace, /prosrc/, /rcp2/, /pe/, /nrcp/) instead of 4; (2) extracts m3u8/mp4 URLs directly from BOTH the rcp page AND the next-hop body so a missing `file:` key no longer kills playback; (3) retries Cloudflare-challenged rcp pages with mobile UA + Sec-Fetch headers; (4) secondary providers (vidsrc.xyz/to/cc, 2embed, embed.su, multiembed, autoembed, moviesapi, smashy) now scrape iframes directly for m3u8/mp4 — ResolveURL is only a backup, so the addon works even when ResolveURL is missing or its plugins are broken.

v1.4.5 — FIX: router was firing every action twice (an extra `if __name__ == '__main__': main()` at the bottom of default.py) — that caused Settings to need 2× OK/Cancel, made stopped videos immediately re-resolve and replay, and doubled every TMDB call. FIX: newer titles that 404 on the primary host (vidsrcme.ru) now silently fall back to vidsrc.xyz → vidsrc.to → vidsrc.net → 2embed.cc using both IMDb and TMDB IDs before giving up. NEW: addon-data cache (`cache_*.json`) is now auto-pruned on every plugin launch (anything older than the TTL is deleted) and a "Clear cache now" button has been added under Settings → Debug. NEW: "Cache TTL (hours)" slider lets you shrink TMDB cache retention.

v1.3.3 — NEW: On Deck row inside TV Shows flags shows where a new episode has aired since you last watched. NEW: Auto-rotating Seasonal row — Halloween Horror (Oct), Christmas (Nov 15 – Dec 31), Valentine's Romance (Feb 1-14) appear inside Movies and TV Shows only when in season. NEW: Ambient Mode item in Movies launches a slow slideshow of fanart from your recently watched titles. NEW: Smart Next-Up — at the end of a TV episode, a countdown prompt auto-plays the next episode (toggle and lead-time in Playback settings).

v1.3.2 — FIX: "Open Settings" menu item no longer shows a "Playback Failed" dialog after closing the settings window (it was marked as a playable item with no resolvable URL). FIX: "Next page »" now works on every Movies / TV / People list (the button was routed to non-existent `movies_page` / `tv_page` / `people_page` actions and silently fell back to the root menu). Each list now remembers its own action + params so pagination works on genres, studios, networks, and popular/top/upcoming lists.

v1.3.1 — Playback FIX: cloudnestra resolver rewritten to survive the latest rcp page layout. Generic iframe / next-hop detection (prorcp, prosrc, rcp2, source, window.location redirects, raw m3u8/mp4 URLs). Cloudflare challenge pages are now detected and automatically fall back to ResolveURL per-server, which understands cloudnestra end-to-end. More verbose diagnostic logging when extraction fails.

v1.3.0 — SIMKL integration added (PIN code at simkl.com/pin). Scrobble start/pause/stop, mark-watched context menu, watched-history sync, continue-watching sync. Works alongside Trakt + Bingebase — enable any combination. Register your free SIMKL app at simkl.com/settings/developer/new/ to get a client ID.

v1.2.0 — Bingebase integration added (device code at bingebase.com/activate). Scrobbling start/pause/stop, mark-watched context menu, two-way sync. Works alongside Trakt — enable one or both.

v1.1.1 — Trakt client preconfigured (no manual key entry needed). Continue Watching row at the top of both Movies and TV Shows submenus. v1.1.0 — Secondary source toggle, server sub-picker, per-show quality memory, Trakt scrobbling, watched / resume indicators, 10 s stall auto-fallback.</news>
    </extension>
</addon>
