<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<addon id="plugin.video.syncher" name="Syncher" version="3.4.0" provider-name="zeus768">
    <requires>
        <import addon="xbmc.python" version="3.0.0"/>
        <import addon="script.module.requests" version="2.25.0"/>
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource" library="main.py">
        <provides>video</provides>
    </extension>
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
        <summary lang="en">Syncher - All-in-One: Movies, TV, Sports, Music (AI), Podcasts, Audiobooks, Radio</summary>
        <description lang="en">Syncher v3.4.0 by zeus768 - The ultimate all-in-one Kodi addon. Movies and TV Shows via Trakt/TMDB with scene release scrapers. Sports Highlights from replay sites. Massive Music section: AI Daily Playlists powered by Emergent Universal Key (like Spotify daily mixes), mood/decade playlists, Deezer charts/genres/artists, user playlists with shuffle/sort/export. Live Radio (30,000+ stations via Radio Browser API). Podcasts via iTunes with RSS episode streaming. Audiobooks via LibriVox and Internet Archive with chapter-by-chapter playback. Resolves through Real-Debrid, Premiumize, AllDebrid, TorBox. AI features powered by Emergent Universal Key.</description>
        <disclaimer lang="en">This addon does not host any content. A debrid service is recommended. AI features require an Emergent Universal Key.</disclaimer>
        <platform>all</platform>
        <license>GPL-3.0-only</license>
        <news>
v3.4.0 (2026)
- NEW: Podcasts section (iTunes Search API)
  * Top podcasts, browse by 19 genres
  * Search podcasts by name
  * Stream episodes directly via RSS feeds
  * Episode metadata with dates and durations
- NEW: Audiobooks section (LibriVox + Internet Archive)
  * 50+ popular classic audiobooks
  * New arrivals from LibriVox
  * Browse by 20 genres
  * Search by title or author
  * Internet Archive search (millions of free audiobooks)
  * Chapter-by-chapter playback with Play All
  * Dual-source: LibriVox API + Internet Archive API
- Updated main menu: Movies, TV, Sports, Music, Podcasts, Audiobooks
- Updated search menu: includes podcast and audiobook search
- AI features use Emergent Universal Key only

v3.3.0 (2026)
- AI Daily Playlists (14 themes, mood, decades, similar artist)
- Live Radio via Radio Browser API
- Enhanced playlists (shuffle, sort, export, import)

v3.2.0 (2026)
- Deezer Music section (genres, artists, albums, charts, playlists)

v2.0.0 (2026)
- Initial release: Movies, TV, Sports, Debrid, Trakt
        </news>
        <assets>
            <icon>icon.png</icon>
            <fanart>fanart.jpg</fanart>
        </assets>
    </extension>
</addon>
