<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<addon id="plugin.video.syncher" name="Syncher" version="3.3.0" provider-name="zeus768">
    <requires>
        <import addon="xbmc.python" version="3.0.0"/>
        <import addon="script.module.requests" version="2.25.0"/>
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource" library="main.py">
        <provides>video</provides>
    </extension>
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
        <summary lang="en">Syncher - Scene Streamer with AI Music, Debrid, Trakt, Deezer, Radio</summary>
        <description lang="en">Syncher v3.3.0 by zeus768 - Browse Movies, TV Shows, Sports Highlights and a massive Music section. AI Daily Playlists powered by Emergent Universal Key (like Spotify Daily Mix), Mood playlists, Decade playlists, Similar Artist AI mixes. Live Radio via Radio Browser API (20+ genres, 20 countries). Full Deezer integration for genres, artists, albums, charts, curated playlists, user playlists with shuffle/sort/export/import and autoplay. Scene release scrapers (RapidRAR, PSA, RapidMoviez, TFPDL, WatchSeriesHD, RLSbb, DDLValley, SceneSource) plus sports replay sites. Resolves through Real-Debrid, Premiumize, AllDebrid, TorBox. Trakt browsing, watchlists, scrobbling. TMDB metadata.</description>
        <disclaimer lang="en">This addon does not host any content. A debrid service or RapidRAR.cr premium account is recommended. AI features require an Emergent Universal Key.</disclaimer>
        <platform>all</platform>
        <license>GPL-3.0-only</license>
        <news>
v3.3.0 (2026)
- NEW: AI Daily Playlists powered by Emergent Universal Key
  * 14 rotating daily themes (Discovery, Chill, Throwback, Workout, etc.)
  * Mood-based playlists (Happy, Sad, Chill, Party, Focus, Workout, etc.)
  * Decade playlists (60s through 2020s best-of)
  * "Similar To..." AI artist mix on any artist page
  * All AI playlists cached daily for speed
- NEW: Live Radio via Radio Browser API (30,000+ stations)
  * Browse by genre (20 categories), country (20 countries)
  * Top voted, most popular, trending stations
  * Search radio stations
- NEW: Enhanced playlists
  * Shuffle play mode
  * Sort by artist or title
  * Export playlist as text
  * Import playlist from text
- AI powered by Emergent Universal Key (set in Settings)

v3.2.0 (2026)
- Rich Music section with Deezer API integration
- Music genres, artists, albums, top charts, curated playlists
- User-created playlists with add/remove tracks
- Auto-play mode for albums and playlists
- Music scene site search

v3.1.1 (2026)
- Version bump and metadata updates

v2.0.0 (2026)
- Initial release: Movies, TV, Sports, Debrid, Trakt, TMDB
        </news>
        <assets>
            <icon>icon.png</icon>
            <fanart>fanart.jpg</fanart>
        </assets>
    </extension>
</addon>
